Hello friends, welcome to my
and your channel, so in today's video
we are going to talk about a new service of CC
where if you
register any person, then you will get
175 instant commission for each registration,
so in this video we are going to
talk about which service and how
one can register in it, after
registering any person,
you will get 175 instant commission,
what is the basic benefit to the people from this service, so
in this video I am going to tell you the complete thing, so
you must watch this video till the end
and if till now you have told by
tweeting here on behalf of our e-government
and here you can see
that there is a great opportunity for the good, that is, there is a
great opportunity for all the good people, from here, in which
if you enroll 1000 citizens
in NPC, then you can become a millionaire from here, that is,
if you earn a millionaire and
here if you  If you enroll 1000 people in NPS,
you can earn up to ₹1 lakh from here. Out of which,
you have been
told here that if you
get an instant commission of Rs.
176, you will be given an instant commission
when you can successfully open an NPS account for any
person. Basically, now
let's talk about what an NPS account
is and what benefits people are going to get.
As you all know that the
NPS service has been launched by the Government of India for all the public, that is,
NPS means National Pension
System, that is, under this,
you
can open an NPS account for all the people here. People get this
benefit. Those who are 18 plus,
you can open an NPS account from here.
Here you all have to make the first payment
from your details and through the portal,
after which every customer
's account will be
auto-deducted ₹500 or ₹1 every month.  After 60
years, they are given some pension, that is,
every month after 60 years, they get Rs.
2000 or 3000 or even more,
depending on how much they want to be deducted from their account,
accordingly, after
60 years, that is,
after 60 years, money is given to them in the form of pension in their account, so in this way,
if there are such people in your area
who want to open an NPS account,
you can open it for them and
you can also open anyone's NPS account by telling someone about it, so if
you do it through the Digital Save Portal, then
you will be given
₹1.75 commission for each account opening here,
so to open an NPS account, you have to
come to the portal from retail and
you will search by writing NPS, after that it will
open in a new tab and from
here you will be
able to open an NPS account for any person, for which
you all have to write from here  As
soon as you click on the option of Login with Digital Seva Connect, then from here you
will click on the SK option to continue, after that after
successfully SKing from here, you will be
able to successfully login into the NPS account i.e. dashboard, then you
can check the NPS calculator of any person from here and
you can also register from here, let me
tell you all that if you want to
open an NPS account for anyone, first of all
calculate his pension and see
how much pension he will get basically, for which you will
click on the pension calculator option, then a
pension calculator will open from here,
for which you will click on the calculate and pensions
option from here, then it will come to you from here from
where you
can calculate the pension and see,
if you open an NPS account for any person,
first of all you will select his date of birth from
here,
whatever is the complete date of birth, you will select it from
here  After selecting, the person for
whom you are opening the NPS account,
how much contribution he wants to make every month, that is, how much he
wants to be debited from his account, you will
select them from here, if any
person has 1000 and let me tell you all that
whatever its return is, it is basically
10 to 12 percent, whatever commission is
given here by the government,
then according to whichever calculation he
will contribute from here, it is
automatically done at 10 percent from here, but basically let me
tell you all that this work basically goes up to 12 percent
and here you people can see
that whatever will be your monthly contribution,
you people can see from here
that
141414, if he gets ₹1 deducted here every
month, then he is given this much pension here
every month after 60 years
and whatever happens here,
how much will he get in total,
how much is given in total percentage for him.  You
can see from here
how much money will be deducted from that person's account and along with
that money,
you can see from here how much total amount will be given from here by adding 12 or 10 from the government side, it
depends on their age and
how much amount they will get, let me tell you all here that
whatever is their date of birth,
according to that, from here they have to get the
money deducted from their account for so many years
and after that, whatever
amount is deducted from their account here
and by
adding the percentage from the government, from here the total
corpus i.e. it is given in the corpus
and whatever is their maturity
after 60 years, in this way,
whatever happens to you starts getting shown from here that
how much pension you will get, so first of all
you calculate this from their date of birth, after going there
you can register the customer from here, if you
click on the customer registration option then you will  You
get three options here that you
can register the customer through three mediums, first of all,
you can register through the DM of your CSC, through the guide from here,
second is that you can register through the society from here
and third is that you can register through self registration from here, that is,
you
can register through your own self from here, for which you can register by
clicking on the self option from here,
self registration will appear from here,
after which you can register any person
for NPS account from here,
if you want to register anyone, then let us
tell you all that
you should register from here only as per your DM
because the
advantage of doing registration through this is that
whatever is pending for you, if there is any
problem in any way, then you can
open that account by guiding it through the DM of CSC, so here
you will enter the PAN card number of the person for whom you are opening the account,
after which you can
submit from here  You will click on the option,
after clicking on the submit option, you all will
get to see an interface like this from
where you all have to complete the registration,
whatever details are there, you fill all the things and
as soon as you complete the registration,
after that you all will get
to see something like this successfully entered from where
you can see that whatever the
payment amount will be, basically
you all have to make a one-time payment of Rs. 500
from your CSC wallet, after which
whatever second payment is made, basically the
account number of the customer which will be linked here, the
money is made every month from the same account number, after which
as soon as you complete the payment from here, only then
you all will
get to see ₹1.76 commission from here, so let me tell you all
that whoever's NPS account you open,
first of all you have to open the NPS account and make the
payment for the first time,
after making the payment, you all will get ₹1.75 or  You will
get ₹1.76 commission, after which the
money will be deducted from the customer's account for every second time. So, in this
way,
you can generate a good income by opening NPS accounts for people around you. So, I hope you
liked this video, then please like it and also
subscribe to our channel.
If you have any inquiry, you
can comment and you will get an
instant reply. See you in the next
video with the next topic. Till then, bye.